▍2026 辛辛那提 WTA1000 1/4决赛
贝莱克 3-6 6-4 7-6(5) 凯斯 · 赛后场上采访
through to your first semi-final
打进了
in a Masters 1000 tournament and boy,
你人生第一个大师赛半决赛
you had your work cut out for you today.
而且这一路走得相当不容易
Yeah, how does it feel?
现在是什么感觉？
I mean, you see you see me right now.
你现在看我这个样子就知道了
It's incredible.
简直难以置信
I'm super happy.
我太开心了
You mixed things up today.
你今天打法很多变
You gave Maddie a hard time.
让凯斯很不好受
A lot of these players are go big
现在很多球员
or go home.
要么放手一搏要么认输
You mixed it up a lot today.
你今天变化打得很多
You knew exactly what to do in order
你很清楚该怎么做
to get yourself out of trouble.
才能从困境里走出来
How proud are you
你对今天这场胜利
of your accomplishment today
有多自豪？
and let's just talk a little bit
我们也聊聊
about what made it so difficult for Maddie
今天凯斯为什么
to take control of this match today?
很难掌控局面？
I was just playing what I felt, how I felt.
我就是凭感觉在打
I wasn't really thinking what should I
没有去想
do, what my coach told me before.
该怎么做 教练之前交代过什么
I totally forgot everything
一上场
when I came on the court.
就把这些全忘了
So,
所以
what I felt I played and yeah,
就跟着感觉去打
that was the key today.
这就是今天获胜的关键
Tell me, before you go off,
在你离开之前问一句
what have you learned about yourself in the
这几天
last few days defeating Aryna Sabalenka,
你先赢了萨巴伦卡
a Grand Slam champion,
一位大满贯冠军
you defeated Madison Keys,
又赢了凯斯
a Grand Slam champion.
也是大满贯冠军
What have you learned about yourself
这几天
in the last few days?
你学到了什么？
Probably to believe.
大概是要相信自己
I believe much more than I ever believed
我比以往任何时候
in myself.
都更相信自己
So, I just keep believing
所以我就一直相信
in the match no matter what and yeah,
不管场上怎样都相信
that's probably the thing which is always
这大概就是
in my head.
我心里一直想的事
Will you watch tonight?
今晚你会看比赛吗？
Marta Kostyuk's playing Coco Gauff.
科斯秋克对阵高芙
I haven't played Coco,
高芙我还没交手过
Marta you've beaten once before.
科斯秋克你之前赢过一次
Will you watch tonight?
你今晚会看吗？
Will you tune it out?
还是不看？
What are your plans for tonight?
今晚有什么安排？
I will take a good dinner.
我要去好好吃顿饭
I will leave this job on my team and let's see
剩下的交给团队
what they will tell me tomorrow and yeah,
看看他们明天怎么安排
I will try to rest and to be ready tomorrow.
我要好好休息 准备好明天
All right, we wish you the best of luck.
好的 祝你好运
Congratulations.
恭喜
High five.
击个掌
She is through to the semi-finals.
她打进了半决赛
Everybody, what a big day
各位 今天真是精彩的一天
Very likable, isn't she?
她真讨人喜欢 对吧？